just uh starting out with Bradley.
>> Yeah.
>> Your thoughts.
>> Um yeah, you know, uh just first with
Bradley, um tremendous amount of respect
for him and Nikki and and his family. Uh
it's been fun to have him around for two
years. Obviously, I was with him in
Baltimore and uh just what he the type
of competitor, leader, and then just
really the people they are in the
community. um to see what he did in
Baltimore with his foundation and then
carry it to Carolina and bring it out to
LA just uh special thing special stuff
they're doing and uh just think the
world of them and I know if he sees this
coach Boseman will end up uh both both
coach Boseman's I believe uh I think I
can see them both back home coaching uh
high school and and imparting their
beliefs and principles in young men and
women. So, um, tremendous amount of
respect for him, appreciation for him,
and love for him and and his family. So,
uh, congrats to him and his retirement
and, you know, plan going forward. Um,
you know, we're we've been discussing
that and, uh, got a new offensive staff,
uh, which leads to some scheme changes.
So, uh, we'll get to we've been meeting,
we'll get together again after the
combine and, uh, we'll have a plan to
attack once once the open season opens.
Yeah, we've talked to either the players
or their agents and we'll continue to
talk to them up until free agency and
into it if we have to.
>> Uh they know they know we want him back.
They know we want it back and I think
that's when when players go into free
agency once the season ends. It takes a
little bit of time, but we'll keep we'll
keep chipping away at it and see if we
can get something done with them.
>> Nothing as far as
>> Yeah, I have no problem having a bunch
of great edge rushers.
>> Uh, no, we have not begun them with
Tulie yet. We got a little bit of time
kind of focused on free agency. Um but
uh we want Tulie around for a long time.
>> It's an it's a possibility. Yeah.
>> I love Keenan. I love him. Look what he
did for us last year.
>> I don't I don't see us tagging anyone
>> right now.
Yeah. Yeah. 22 year olds are young now,
right? It's it's it's a really neat
dynamic. Um, you know, with COVID, with
players staying for the fourth or fifth
year because of NIL, you definitely have
an older crop this year. I think it'll
level out a little bit going forward
once we're clear of the COVID sixes, you
know, the guys that got the extra year
of COVID and the the um in the red
shirt, but um it should level out some,
but you never know. Um you know, the
age, they're still older, but the whole
class is a whole is older. So, when you
when you see a 20-year-old or a 21-y
old, you're like, "Wow, this guy's a
baby now." You know, and uh they were
young, but they're almost more rare now.
So,
Um, I think everyone always has upside.
I really do. I think there's players
that are 28 years old that that can get
better. Um, you just get them with with,
you know, new coaching, new strength
programs. You know, I see what Ben
Herbert does at our place and uh he
brings vets in and uh he makes a big
impact on them as fifth, sixth, seventh
year vets. So, uh, there's always upside
in players, but yeah, you know, I think
as a whole, you you say a guy who's 21
is going to grow more those four years
versus a guy who's 25 in the draft.
>> Are you expecting to address that?
>> Um, we will try.
um both. Um you know, I that's why
there's three receivers out there on the
field, right? You got guys that can just
shake away from a defender like that and
then there's guys that can catch the
back shoulder or contested ball on the
sideline. Um I think if you have a
complement of all types of receivers,
you help your team. If you have three
that do the same thing and nobody can
catch contested, they all can separate.
That's good. But at some point, you're
going to need someone that can make the
contested catch, especially when the
field shrinks in the red zone. So, I
think they both both types of receivers
have value for the league.
>> I mean, I think both receivers are tough
to find. I think, you know, you just
take shots at it. Um there's some guys
that specialize in contested balls, you
know. Um you know, so I feel like we
have a good complement of both on our
team and uh so to say which is harder to
find, I don't know. You know, guys that
can separate are tough to find, like
truly separate. Um but to find the guy
that can catch the make the 50/50 ball
and 8020 ball, they're hard to find,
too. So, you know, you just keep you
keep looking, keep taking shots for him.
Oh, yeah. My I Jesse I love um you know
I it's funny I talked to Eric through
the process and uh we all remember Jesse
as a young coach and uh just to get back
with him in Los Angeles and see how he's
grown as a as a play caller as a leader.
Um, you know, it's different when you're
a safeties coach or a defensive
assistant and a safeties coach and then
you're put in front of a a room to lead.
And to see how well he handled that in
Los Angeles, um, uh, was just amazing.
And not only his ability to lead the
room, uh, to communicate, but then the
way he interacts with everyone in the
building, his ability to evaluate
players, evaluate staffs, coaches. I
He's put together a great staff there in
Baltimore. And uh so love love Jesse and
uh really developed a great friendship.
Hate to see him go, but love to see
where he ended up.
Yeah. Uh my first my first reaction I
was a little surprised because the
continuity having been there for 26
years I knew how important it was but um
definitely uh understand the move and I
and and and see and I also see what it
allowed for happen with John too and uh
happy for John as well and and happy for
the Ravens and uh I think if Jesse just
is himself he'll be just fine you know
he'll be able to fill the shoes and and
he'll fill him in his own way.
What's the plan with him?
>> The Yeah, those are things that we'll
discuss. We get back Sunday, all the
coaches and staff will meet Monday,
Tuesday, Wednesday, and we'll finalize
all those plans then.
>> I'm not going to talk about that right
now. R
>> uh it's been fun, man. Um the whole
process was a blast. Um myself, coach
and Chad sat in all the offensive co
coordinator interviews and you really
got to just listen to ball and
philosophy and um really great u Mike's
just great person, great soul, uh great
ideas, great energy, brought it, you
know, a lot of his staff in and just
they bring great energy to the room.
There's excitement um about what we're
going to do and uh he's so excited about
it. So, his excitement rubs off on on
you right away. And uh but really
looking forward to it. He's been we've
discussed some players in free agency.
He'll get more involved in the draft
process now once we go through the
combine. Uh but I'm really looking
forward to he's he's been an evaluator
his whole life, you know, and uh and he
loves he loves this part of the process.
So, uh I'm looking forward to it.
like that.
>> Yeah. You know, I I if if a guy hasn't
called plays, I say give him a shot
because I didn't I I didn't GM before I
GM, right? You know, and uh I think what
you do is as a as a young coach If your
goal is to become a play caller, well,
who do you attach yourself to? The play
caller, you know, and you learn how to
call plays. And heard some really neat
answers from from some coaches on both
sides of the ball during our coordinator
searches about how they prepare, how
they would prepare, how they did prepare
their first year where they'd watch
games and they'd call the play off a
live broadcast. And I think there's ways
a guy can can set himself up to be ready
to roll. And uh but you just, you know,
if you're hiring a a coordinator who's
never called plays, you know, you want
to find a smart guy who can handle the
moment.
>> How different is the approach to
personnel?
>> Yeah, I think the biggest is is uh is
the offensive line. Uh you know, we went
through it in Baltimore. I think in 2014
when we hired Gary Kubak, uh we went to
the wide zone and and so the the draft
process when when you do that, it kind
of changes how you evaluate a player in
the fall versus uh here we are in in
February and March when you're
evaluating the player. So, you have to
understand that there's going to be some
uh variability or some the players will
move a little bit more on the board than
normal because hey, this guy in our old
scheme may have fit better, doesn't fit
as well now. So, um, but scouts, scouts
know how to evaluate for all positions.
We've been doing it our whole careers
before Mike got here. This guy's more of
his own scheme fit. So, now that being
said in a report, okay, well, he fits us
now.
>> So, fair to say more.
>> Yeah. Uh, yeah. More just more range,
you know, guys that can get to the cut
off blocks and reach and get out in
space.
I I I do. I do. And uh I think last year
with us and I think about they honestly
I've said like some of our in Baltimore
our worst years is when we had you know
some struggles on the O line or got beat
up and and uh you know this last year
was a rare year for us and it's a
testament to all the players. We had a
lot of injuries in Los Angeles about,
you know, on the O line and uh testament
to all the guys to overcome it and uh
but yeah, you control the lines, you're
going to be in a good chance to to win
the game at the end
>> with
your sense of
>> Yeah, we have a range with every player,
not just Zion, with every player that
that we tag a guy with a range. change
and uh there's evaluation and so that's
that's what we do and uh you know is it
a hard is it a hard ceiling no I don't
think you ever place a hard ceiling on
any player but you have to you have to
pay what you think a player is worth or
somewhere near there and uh so yeah
we'll see what happens with Zion where
the market goes if he gets to the market
but we'll stay engaged with them through
the process contracts impact
>> uh we'll see you know you know That's
just we'll be we'll meet with his agent
this week and and uh and we've talked to
him already and we'll continue to the
dialogue.
>> You got to have one to take. You got to
have one to take. Um listen, you can't
just The position is incredibly
valuable, right? And uh but you still
have to be convicted that this can be
the guy uh that'll lead your
organization going forwards. And listen,
it's hard to find a a really talented
quarterback, starting quarterback in the
NFL. So, um you don't want to throw away
picks because that pick does have value,
whether it's a quarterback or any
position. You could take, you know,
anything and you get more value after
taking a quarterback you don't like.
our existing situation.
>> I mean, I would just say if you got a
guy you like, you take him. You know, if
not, take another position.
>> We'll make that decision shortly. We
have we have till May for that one.
Yeah. Um, well, you know, I think Mike's
got some good ideas uh in terms of
protect the ways to protect Justin. Um,
and then uh listen, we're always going
to try to help Justin and that's
throwing more players at all at all
positions to help the team. And um so
we're going to attack the O line, we're
going to attack the defense, we're going
to attack the backs, tight ends,
everything. you know, wide outs. We The
more weapons and more players we can put
around Justin, the better we protect
Justin.
>> I'm not going to tip my hand on any
players right now.
>> Tyler,
>> I'm not going to talk about any players
under contract with other teams. I'm not
going to do it.
I'm not going to speak in hypotheticals.
Nice try though.
>> As far as working hard,
>> um the coolest thing about college
scouting that we always had to answer,
right, when we were going to schools, um
how's a guy going to be when he has
money? Now we have that answer. So some
guys get the money and and change the
way they are. Other guys get the money
like and change a bit. He spend you know
you hear stories about takes his guys
out for dinner. He spends his NIL money
on his teammates. Work hard leader. So
you kind of get the answer and so it's
it's actually a it's a great thing in a
sense and it's great for the players,
you know, in college to to have that
opportunity to to make some money
>> with how little
>> I'm sorry.
Well, you know, just his plan, um, his
intelligence, his energy, charisma. Now,
we knew a lot of that from when he was
here, but his prep his preparedness for
the interview, we I talked to Chris uh
before uh Jesse actually got a job. I
just said, "Hey, listen. If Jesse's got
eight at the time, eight and ended up
being nine interviews, and we'd like to
interview, see if we can get it set up
and uh we had a chance to interview him
down in Mobile and just his energy, his
creativity, his ideas for going forward,
not just this is what I did, but this is
what I want to learn and uh I just just
did a great job.
>> No, we No,
>> I think uh he didn't surprise me because
I knew how how talented he was when he
was here in 2024. Uh but he he did what
I thought he would do to say we had a
favorite. No, we had we were looking
inside and externally and so we had
interviewed a lot of great candidates
both internally and externally and uh a
number of guys could do the job but we
just felt he was the best option.
>> Oh, I think anytime you can do it,
someone asked a question earlier about
calling plays. Um anytime you gain that
confidence doing it for a year, um I'm
sure that'll help him. Um, but he uh he
he he's a he's a great coordinator in
the sense that he knows his staff makes
him a great coordinator and great play
caller. So, he'll rely on on on all the
guys in the room and uh put together
something good. Mr.